Oh, it's you...
How are you?
I'm glad everyone's having fun, but honestly, I'm kind of worried.
Kharyskhan almost killed us all, and now I have the responsibility of making Isa a part of the world again... a part of Sarnaut!
You can always count on me!
I'm glad you're willing to help! I would like to think that my new brothers will help me. But... it's also difficult! I have always been alone.
I don’t know what a real sister should do! Besides, we are so different…
Out there, outside of Isa, many believe in the light and have the ability to resurrect, and we know that the Thread of every being is finite. What will happen to our sprout, then?
I think there will be a common fate
Good. I wouldn't want to be alone again! Life is easier with brothers!
How will your saga end?
Oh! I've almost finished it! Here: There were three of them now: Trondur, Wickham, and Gerda! Thread Keepers are with them,
They are ready to help with the Tree. The ritual was performed The dark spell was lifted The tree blossomed again Isa was saved! Now we can go
On a journey A ship was built By a Gibberling family. Their path lies Through the Void which is boundless Many things await them
And endless adventures! Brave brothers Their sister with a harp Has become a great skald Everyone knows her now! Do you think it will come true?
Absolutely!
I'm glad you think so! So it really will!
Can we sit here a little longer?
Alright